because I know that Issa is doing
something within this business that so
few people get to do and it's not
something I desire to do like I'm I'm
not interested in getting a $100 million
production deal like that's not a life
that I want for myself but I know that
her role is very important and so I've
always protected Issa um however there's
just been enough instances at this point
where I should have been protected by
Issa and I wasn't and one of my biggest
problems that we have discussed several
times in this interview is that I I
think people are going to show up for me
the way I show up for them and now it's
at a point where my protecting of Issa
has become turned on to me and something
that people are using against me there's
a whole narrative that is completely
false that people keep spinning they
keep saying you know that I'm this mean
girl on this set that I that I uh that I
harm these people on this set I just
want to point out something very basic
how can I be a mean girl on a set that
ain't my
set how how it's your show you are my
boss I don't even have the